[
  {"question": "ア", "choices": ["a", "ka", "na", "sa"], "answer": "a"},
  {"question": "イ", "choices": ["e", "i", "o", "u"], "answer": "i"},
  {"question": "ウ", "choices": ["u", "a", "e", "o"], "answer": "u"},
  {"question": "エ", "choices": ["i", "e", "u", "a"], "answer": "e"},
  {"question": "オ", "choices": ["u", "o", "a", "e"], "answer": "o"},
  {"question": "カ", "choices": ["ka", "ki", "ko", "ku"], "answer": "ka"},
  {"question": "キ", "choices": ["ku", "ke", "ki", "ko"], "answer": "ki"},
  {"question": "ク", "choices": ["ka", "ku", "ki", "ko"], "answer": "ku"},
  {"question": "ケ", "choices": ["ke", "ki", "ko", "ka"], "answer": "ke"},
  {"question": "コ", "choices": ["ku", "ko", "ke", "ki"], "answer": "ko"},
  {"question": "サ", "choices": ["sa", "shi", "se", "so"], "answer": "sa"},
  {"question": "シ", "choices": ["shi", "sa", "su", "se"], "answer": "shi"},
  {"question": "ス", "choices": ["su", "se", "so", "shi"], "answer": "su"},
  {"question": "セ", "choices": ["so", "shi", "se", "sa"], "answer": "se"},
  {"question": "ソ", "choices": ["sa", "so", "se", "su"], "answer": "so"},
  {"question": "タ", "choices": ["ta", "chi", "tsu", "te"], "answer": "ta"},
  {"question": "チ", "choices": ["chi", "tsu", "te", "ta"], "answer": "chi"},
  {"question": "ツ", "choices": ["tsu", "chi", "te", "to"], "answer": "tsu"},
  {"question": "テ", "choices": ["te", "to", "ta", "tsu"], "answer": "te"},
  {"question": "ト", "choices": ["to", "tsu", "ta", "chi"], "answer": "to"},
  {"question": "ナ", "choices": ["na", "ni", "ne", "no"], "answer": "na"},
  {"question": "ニ", "choices": ["ni", "na", "nu", "ne"], "answer": "ni"},
  {"question": "ヌ", "choices": ["nu", "ne", "ni", "no"], "answer": "nu"},
  {"question": "ネ", "choices": ["ne", "nu", "ni", "na"], "answer": "ne"},
  {"question": "ノ", "choices": ["no", "ne", "nu", "ni"], "answer": "no"},
  {"question": "ハ", "choices": ["ha", "hi", "fu", "he"], "answer": "ha"},
  {"question": "ヒ", "choices": ["hi", "fu", "ho", "he"], "answer": "hi"},
  {"question": "フ", "choices": ["fu", "ho", "he", "ha"], "answer": "fu"},
  {"question": "ヘ", "choices": ["he", "fu", "hi", "ho"], "answer": "he"},
  {"question": "ホ", "choices": ["ho", "hi", "fu", "he"], "answer": "ho"},
  {"question": "マ", "choices": ["ma", "mi", "mu", "me"], "answer": "ma"},
  {"question": "ミ", "choices": ["mi", "mu", "me", "mo"], "answer": "mi"},
  {"question": "ム", "choices": ["mu", "me", "mi", "ma"], "answer": "mu"},
  {"question": "メ", "choices": ["me", "mo", "ma", "mu"], "answer": "me"},
  {"question": "モ", "choices": ["mo", "me", "mu", "ma"], "answer": "mo"},
  {"question": "ヤ", "choices": ["ya", "yu", "yo", "wa"], "answer": "ya"},
  {"question": "ユ", "choices": ["yu", "yo", "ya", "wa"], "answer": "yu"},
  {"question": "ヨ", "choices": ["yo", "ya", "yu", "wa"], "answer": "yo"},
  {"question": "ラ", "choices": ["ra", "ri", "ru", "re"], "answer": "ra"},
  {"question": "リ", "choices": ["ri", "ru", "re", "ro"], "answer": "ri"},
  {"question": "ル", "choices": ["ru", "re", "ro", "ra"], "answer": "ru"},
  {"question": "レ", "choices": ["re", "ro", "ra", "ri"], "answer": "re"},
  {"question": "ロ", "choices": ["ro", "re", "ru", "ri"], "answer": "ro"},
  {"question": "ワ", "choices": ["wa", "wo", "ya", "ra"], "answer": "wa"},
  {"question": "ヲ", "choices": ["wo", "wa", "yo", "o"], "answer": "wo"},
  {"question": "ン", "choices": ["n", "na", "ne", "ni"], "answer": "n"},
  {"question": "ガ", "choices": ["ga", "ka", "gi", "go"], "answer": "ga"},
  {"question": "ギ", "choices": ["gi", "ga", "ge", "go"], "answer": "gi"},
  {"question": "グ", "choices": ["gu", "ga", "gi", "go"], "answer": "gu"},
  {"question": "ゲ", "choices": ["ge", "gi", "ga", "go"], "answer": "ge"},
  {"question": "ゴ", "choices": ["go", "ga", "gi", "gu"], "answer": "go"},
  {"question": "ザ", "choices": ["za", "ji", "ze", "zo"], "answer": "za"},
  {"question": "ジ", "choices": ["ji", "za", "zu", "zo"], "answer": "ji"},
  {"question": "ズ", "choices": ["zu", "ze", "zo", "ji"], "answer": "zu"},
  {"question": "ゼ", "choices": ["ze", "zo", "zu", "za"], "answer": "ze"},
  {"question": "ゾ", "choices": ["zo", "zu", "ze", "ji"], "answer": "zo"},
  {"question": "ダ", "choices": ["da", "de", "do", "za"], "answer": "da"},
  {"question": "ヂ", "choices": ["ji", "di", "da", "zu"], "answer": "ji"},
  {"question": "ヅ", "choices": ["zu", "ji", "da", "de"], "answer": "zu"},
  {"question": "デ", "choices": ["de", "da", "do", "ze"], "answer": "de"},
  {"question": "ド", "choices": ["do", "de", "da", "du"], "answer": "do"},
  {"question": "バ", "choices": ["ba", "pa", "ha", "da"], "answer": "ba"},
  {"question": "ビ", "choices": ["bi", "pi", "hi", "gi"], "answer": "bi"},
  {"question": "ブ", "choices": ["bu", "pu", "fu", "gu"], "answer": "bu"},
  {"question": "ベ", "choices": ["be", "pe", "he", "ge"], "answer": "be"},
  {"question": "ボ", "choices": ["bo", "po", "ho", "go"], "answer": "bo"},
  {"question": "パ", "choices": ["pa", "ba", "ha", "da"], "answer": "pa"},
  {"question": "ピ", "choices": ["pi", "bi", "hi", "gi"], "answer": "pi"},
  {"question": "プ", "choices": ["pu", "bu", "fu", "gu"], "answer": "pu"},
  {"question": "ペ", "choices": ["pe", "be", "he", "ge"], "answer": "pe"},
  {"question": "ポ", "choices": ["po", "bo", "ho", "go"], "answer": "po"}
]
